

Ayush Kumar Student

My Contact

ak0224225@gmail.com

+91 9582094331

T-510/C-15E, New Delhi-08

www.codewithayu.weebly.com

Hard Skill

- C, C++, JAVA, RenPy, Shell Script (Basic)
- Problem Solver
- Troubleshooting
- Presentation Skills
- · Writing skills

Soft Skill

- Adaptive
- Decision making
- Communication
- Fast Learner

Education Background

- PUSA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY
 Electronics and Communication with 89.6%
 Currently Pursuing
- P.G D.A.V SEN. SEC. School 10th with 81.2% marks
 Completed in 2020

About Me

Currently a student at PUSA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY from ECE Branch. Have 1 year of coding experience in JAVA and currently learning RenPy. My future goal is to get a job in which I can help others using my skills in coding and my knowledge in Electronics.

Professional Experience

Max Engg. and Automation | Intern

June 2022 - July 2022

Key learnings:

- Learnt about PLC, SCADA, Vijeo designer basic
- Learnt the ladder language for PLC Programming

Bentext Pvt. Ltd. | Intern

May 2022 - June 2022

Key learnings:

- Learnt about **Electric meter**
- Learnt about Its circuit
- Prepared reports on the above information and reported the insights.

Achievements

2022-2023 Developed many programs like

Calculator, Attendance Register,
Music Player, I Wonder (Visual Novel)
using Java and RenPy and uploaded
them on GitHub and my website.

2021-2022 Developed many (almost 100) **custom**

roms for Redmy Y1 and Y1 lite and was acknowledged by Nippon and

Cafebabe (Poppular developers)

Projects

6th sem **Automatic Door opening system** using

Arduino as Major Project.

4th sem Wireless Charger as Minor Project.